(Leonard:)Come on, I'll help you pick something.
(Raj:)That's right. She's with us.
(Raj:)Guys like that are so pathetic.
(Howard:)Tell me about it.
Ooh, look, a new Batman belt buckle.
(Store clerk:)Oh, hey, Leonard.
I help you find something?
(Leonard:)Oh, hey, Stuart. This is Penny.
She's just looking for some comic books.
Oh, really? Wow. Blink twice
if you're here against your will.
(Leonard:)I think we're fine, Stuart.
- Okay. Let me know if you need anything.
- Thanks.
Oh, he seems like a nice guy.
(Leonard:)You mean for someone
who's into comic books?
No, no, no. I just meant for... Yeah.
(Leonard:)Just because people appreciate comic
books doesn't make them weirdoes.
(Leonard:)Stuart's a terrific artist. He went
to the Rhode Island School of Design.
Okay, what about the guy in the superhero
T-shirt tucked into his sweatpants?